proverbs chapter 6 verse 23 the Bible
says for the commandment is they watts
lamp and the law is light and reproof of
instructions are the way of life the
Bible says that when we keep the
commandments we are lightening up how
many of you want to lighten up but love
any law is fulfilled in one word and
that word is love how do you lighten up
love love many of us cannot lighten up
because we don't know how to love and in
fact the Bible says in first John 2:10
he that loveth his brother abideth in
the light and there is no occasion of
stumbling in him you want to lighten up
how many of you want to lighten up love
your brother I don't mean your blood
brother you're like oh that's easy I
love well it's not so easy but I love
them anyway no no we're not talking
about your blood brother we're not even
talking about your blood relative we're
not even talking about your friends love
your brother pray for those who use you
despitefully you want to lighten up you
got to learn how to love reason many of
us can't lighten up reason that light
cannot fall upon us it's powerful
because in the writings of spirit of
prophecy she says at the end of time I
saw people going forth and their faces
were lighted up with the glory of God
but that cannot be us if we don't know
how to love that cannot be us if we're
not understanding the time we're living
in that cannot be yes if salvation is
not within us that cannot be us if the
Holy Spirit is not dwelling in us what
I'm trying to tell you church is that we
need to lighten up we need to learn how
to love the Bible says in Matthew 24:12
because iniquity shall abound the love
of many shall do Watts Watts cold
we can't lighten up because we don't
know how to love
our love has waxed cold there's a fifth
way to help you lighten up Matthew
chapter 5 verse 14 Matthew chapter 5
verse 14 Jesus said there you are the
light of the world a city that is set on
the hill cannot be he neither do men
light a candle and put it under a bushel
but on a candlestick that it may give
light unto all that are in the house let
your light so shine before men that they
may see your what good works and glorify
your father which is in heaven
you like being nice lighting up being
guys I think about it how can I help my
neighbor you know that parable of the
Good Samaritan learn how to be a good
Samaritan that's how you can bring light
to a world that is in darkness
let your this little light of a mother
sing it but you know I'm gonna let it
shine that's all God is asking he's just
saying guys just do me a favor that's
all I'm asking you to do just lighten up
and the way you do it is by allowing my
presence my spirit my power to dwell in
you the reason I want you to lighten up
is because this world is in darkness the
sixth way to lighten up Daniel chapter
12 verse 3 Daniel chapter 12 verse 3 the
Bible says here Daniel 12 verse 3 and
they that be wise they that be one every
one why shall shine as the brightness of
the firmament and they that turn many to
watch righteousness as the stars for
ever and ever do you realize that when
you win a soul when you share the gospel
with others you are in essence
lightening up God just says just lighten
up guys why are you so
all down with the things of this world
lighten up and do what I ask you to do
we come the Church of tired and hmm
Jesus like I need you to go out into the
world and lighten up and you can't
lighten up because you got so much going
on which leads to that seventh principle
of lighting up Hebrews chapter 12 verse